𝗕𝘂𝘀𝗶𝗻𝗲𝘀𝘀 𝗽𝗿𝗼𝗯𝗹𝗲𝗺:
The UK Department of Transport provides open datasets on road safety and casualties, and one can
use these datasets to analyze how safe the roads in the UK are. This project will help you answer a
few questions using their 2015 dataset.
The dataset has 3 tables i.e Accident, vehicle, Vehicle_type


𝗔𝗽𝗽𝗿𝗼𝗮𝗰𝗵/𝗣𝗿𝗼𝗷𝗲𝗰𝘁 𝗜𝗱𝗲𝗮
Use aggregate functions in SQL and Python to answer the following sample questions:
1. Evaluate the median severity value of accidents caused by various Motorcycles.
2. Evaluate Accident Severity and Total Accidents per Vehicle Type
3. Calculate the Average Severity by vehicle type.
4. Calculate the Average Severity and Total Accidents by Motorcycle.